pennystockprophet.com 2013-06-07

# Privacy | The Penny Stock Prophet

### Privacy policy

Pennystockprophet.com guarantees that it will not directly or through any affiliate, disclose to, sell, lease, or rent to any nonaffiliated third party your e-mail address, physical address, or non-public information, in anyway whatsoever.   Pennystockprophet.com understands that your privacy is extremely important and will take the necessary steps to protect your privacy.   

**Information Use:**   Pennystockprophet.com collects personal information when you register to receive information, such as an email address.  You are no longer anonymous once you register.  We limit access to personal information about you to Pennystockprophet.com employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with you to provide products or services to you in order to fulfill their work duties.  Only under the following circumstances would we ever use your information: 

-We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Pennystockprophet.com's terms of use or as otherwise required by law: 

-We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

-We transfer your information due to a merger or other business acquisition.  In any event you will be notified before any changes take place via email, or as a posted message on our website.  

-We decide to notify you about a related service or product that is an addition to the Pennystockprophet.com newsletter. 

**Information Restrictions:**   Pennystockprophet.com forbids the use of our services or lists in any manner to send any unsolicited bulk or unsolicited commercial e-mail.  Pennystockprophet.com forbids the collection of email addresses or other information from or through the Pennystockprophet.com services.   Pennystockprophet.com does not permit any attempt to use its services in a way that could damage or impair any of the Pennystockprophet.com services or that would interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of any Pennystockprophet.com service. 

**Affiliates:** We are not responsible for the actions of our affiliates or others who may choose to advertise this Site and or its products/services. All of our ClickBank affiliates must remember that they have agreed to ClickBank's "client contract" which outlines the rules and regulations they have agreed to follow. These terms can be found at the following URL: <http://www.clickbank.com/terms.html>. Affiliates may not under any circumstance send out unsolicited mailings (spam) of any sort. Do not send any mailings to those other than your own opt-in subscribers. If you ignore this warning and proceed to distribute spam, you will likely be rejected by ClickBank, your ISP, and your host, and you could be sued. Termination from this program will be immediate for any spam violation, and all commissions and contest winnings will be revoked.  

**Governing Law:**   Pennystockprophet.com's privacy policy and the use of the website are governed by in our personal jurisdiction and city, state and country of our physical location.    

**Changes to Privacy Policy:** Pennystockprophet.com has the right to update or change its policy at any time.   If changes are made, we will notify you via email any significant changes in the way we treat your personal information to the primary email address registered to your Pennystockprophet.com membership, or posting a message on our website.
